I will be sharing
10 Best stocks
yes you heard it right!
below their 52 week high
that make a good buy for the long term
these 10 growth stocks range from large cap to small cap
these are from finance, chemical, technology etc
But do you know the best part?
I want you to participate in this video too
You can vote for one out of these ten stocks
on which you want me to make a fundamental analysis video
So do watch the story of these 10 stocks
understand their business fundamentals
and comment the stock's name, for which I will make a video for you guys
first stock, is a large cap banking stock
and its 12% below its 52 week high
this stock has consistently shown growth in sales and profits
and this share is Kotak Mahindra Bank
now you must be questioning
why did Kotak's share get corrected
in the last quarter, their non performing assets have increased
Gross npa increased from 3.25% to 3.56%
net npa increased from 1.21% to 1.28% QoQ
There are chances this phenomenon is temporary
since the last quarter was affected by COVID
Infact even Insurance is a sector where opportunities have been created
I will cover that in this video, shortly
If I talk about Kotak's business
The best part is they are technologically adaptive
Kotak, for their banks
incorporate new technologies like Robotic process automation
WhatsApp banking, Chatbots etc.
are used actively.
Kotak's price to book ratio is 4 plus
which is one the higher side
but its moderated due to recent correction
Kotak Bank's support is around 1700
and has strong resistance around 1820
for long term, they have support around 1450
now if you guys want a detailed analysis
don't forget to drop a comment for Kotak
Next stock has a market cap of 65000 cr
In this stock there's been a 36% CAGR profit growth
and 22% CAGR sales growth is seen
its corrected at 8% below 52 week high
and this stock is ICICI Lombard
In the last quarter they've got a lot of claims due to COVID
which clearly impacted their results
Combined ratio is an important parameter in insurance
the sum of losses and expenses and dividing it by the premium
CR for ICICI has gone from 99.7% to 120%
this is a very positive signal
there are other parameters like combined ratio in insurance business
its evaluated in a different way
I'd like to share a fun fact with you all
General Insurance Comapnies don't rely on premium for profits
If you want me to make a video on ICICI
Don't forget to comment this name
In coming times, there are several factors
which can boost the general insurance business
India's penetration for insurance is less
This can be a huge theme for coming years
Second, increasing vaccination drive.
Decreasing Covid cases
This will boost health insurance business
If we talk about the support levels
It has a strong support around 1410
It has two strong resistances
at 1520 and at around 1620
Third stock, has 40000 cr market cap
and specialises in off road tyres
Their business segments are agriculture
Industrial, Mining, Construction
65% of their revenue is from agriculture
this stock is 10% below its 52 week high
I am talking about Balkrishna Industries
Balkrishna Industries has shown  sales growth of around 7%
Last year they've shown sales of around 2,27,000MT
This year, i.e., FY22
They've shown guidance in range 2,50,000-2,65,000MT
which is a very positive sign
35% expense from overall is of raw materials
Synthetic rubber is their raw material
So if the prices for rubber fluctuate, it risks the company
They've also planned a CAPEX for 1900 Cr
To improve their equipment and capacities
This CAPEX is a positive sign
for the coming years
currently this stock is very close to its support level
which is around 2230
But here I would like to caution all investors
Since its shown a strong up move last year
Do you want to see a detailed fundamental analysis for Balkrishna Industries?
Do tell me in the comments
Our next stock has 6%+ correction
It's a city gas distribution company
Their business is across 6 states, 1 UT and 43 districts
And I'm talking about Gujarat Gas
They primarily distribute Natural Gas
Natural Gas is cleaner as compared to other Fossil Fuels
Government actively supports clean fuels
Gujarat Gas has 550+ Gas Stations
150 have been set up last year itself
Expect volume to grow at 10% CAGR
which is very positive
Govt also plans to offer 65 new licenses
Govt also proposes to aid new players in this domain
This is a competition risk
If this gets implemented
Their first support level is around 682
Second major support is around 503
Next stock is a clear beneficiary of the stock market boom
It stands 23% below its 52 week high
their market cap is around 12000 cr
This is a mid cap company with a promising business
And this stock is CDSL
CDSL primarily is a depository service
basically it maintains asset classes in the digital form
We'll discuss another such company shortly
If I extend this thought process more then
CDSL already has an existing business
Or they plan to extend in other asset class
Insurance, Foreign Depository, Commodities etc
Primary factors that drive CDSL's growth:
In recent years no. of retails investors has increased
and for this active depository services are needed
with this, increasing financial awareness
and a complete digital ecosystem
works in the favor of this company
CDSL is attractive at the current levels
Its support is around 1100 and
long term major support is around 955
and the resistance is around 1261
If this stock closes decisively above 1261
there could be a momentum in this stock
So friends, you are consuming this stock market related content
if you believe in stock market participation
and growth then
Do vote for CDSL in comments
I will cover 2 stories in the next section
One is an AI based company
Which is 34% below their 52 week high
the other stock is an agro chemical company
And its 11% below its 52 week high
and the stocks I'm talking about are Affle
and Sumitomo Chemicals!
I've covered these stocks in detail
will paste the links in description
Do watch those video!
Our next stock is a pharma company
And its 6% below its 52 week high
Their business fundamentals are strong
And they have a competitive advantage
In injectables' business
And this stock is Gland Pharma
Govt has allocated an additional 137% budget
to the pharma industry
there will be a lot of growth factors
Chronic diseases have become prevalent
and there are new innovations like pen injectors
basically, injecting medicine to yourself
Rising use of making medicines from living organisms
this will also be prevalent in coming times
and pharma is one such business with lots of entry barriers
so no competition can enter easily
Its support is around 3950 and
and second support is around 3100
I would like to caution you here
this stock has shown a one way upside movement here
This can be a risky bet
and we should keep this in mind
Gland pharma has very strong business fundamentals
and if you guys want to see a complete fundamental analysis
don't forget to vote for it
Our next company is also from the Pharma sector
It is a diagnostic company
The last quarters' results were good
And its 13% below its 52 week high
And this stock is Metropolis Healthcare
Rising healthcare awareness
ageing population
and rising disposable incomes
all this would boost Metropolis' business
It's a strong franchise in diagnostics' space
the covid cases are falling
and there's rising vaccinations
and this would reduce the number of tests
and overall the diagnostics sector would have a muted performance
However the long term trend seems intact
And this could benefit metropolis healthcare
currently, its support is around 2600
and its long term support seems at 2300
The last stock is a small cap multibagger
This video is not a stock market recommendation
It  is only meant for educational purposes
Please consult your financial advisor before any investment decision.
This stock had a recent IPO
And its 15% below its all time high
It's an agro chemical company
It has a 3000 cr market cap
And this company is Heranba Industries
It is a small cap company
Small Cap companies are more risky
However this company has good business prospects
Heranba is a leading manufacturer of Pyrethroids
Pyrethroids are made of Pyrethrin
which is found in chrysanthemum
Which means they are made of naturally occurring things
hence they are less toxic or harmful
in coming times, globally and domestically
pesticides made from naturally occurring substances'
use is bound to increase
I've already covered Heranba in detail
Will paste the link in description
But if you guys want a detailed analysis on Heranba
So don't forget to vote for Heranba
There's not much in the charts due to its recent listing
It's support 1 is around 800
and a more long term support is around 720
I would like to share another thing with you here
We've made a list of 10 mid cap multibaggers before
and 6 small cap multibaggers have been covered
Do watch and like those videos!